<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://sarahmbrown.org</id>
  <title> Sarah M Brown</title>
  <updated>2024-03-17T03:47:00.555797+00:00</updated>
  <link href="https://sarahmbrown.org"/>
  <link href="https://sarahmbrown.org/news/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://ablog.readthedocs.org/" version="0.10.33.post1">ABlog</generator>
  <entry>
    <id>https://sarahmbrown.org/news/2023-07-31-tdssp23/</id>
    <title>I’m teaching CS for Talent Development Summer Success Program</title>
    <updated>2023-07-31T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;div class="ablog-post-excerpt docutils container"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am co-teaching Active Learning in Computer Science and leading CS Thinking and learning for the Talent Development Summer Success Program.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
    <link href="https://sarahmbrown.org/news/2023-07-31-tdssp23/"/>
    <summary>I am co-teaching Active Learning in Computer Science and leading CS Thinking and learning for the Talent Development Summer Success Program.</summary>
    <published>2023-07-31T00:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://sarahmbrown.org/news/2023-09-10-ugfa23/</id>
    <title>Welcome to new Undergraduate Researchers Kyle and Brendan</title>
    <updated>2023-09-10T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;div class="ablog-post-excerpt docutils container"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kyle will be working on applying ML to Antimicrobial Peptide (AMP) design.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brendan will be working on softare improvements to internal tools used in the lab.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
    <link href="https://sarahmbrown.org/news/2023-09-10-ugfa23/"/>
    <summary>Kyle will be working on applying ML to Antimicrobial Peptide (AMP) design.Brendan will be working on softare improvements to internal tools used in the lab.</summary>
    <published>2023-09-10T00:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://sarahmbrown.org/news/2024-01-18-aisummit/</id>
    <title>I presented on What is AI at the Academic Summit for URI Faculty</title>
    <updated>2024-01-18T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;div class="ablog-post-excerpt docutils container"&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
    <link href="https://sarahmbrown.org/news/2024-01-18-aisummit/"/>
    <published>2024-01-18T00:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://sarahmbrown.org/news/2024-01-23-ugsp24/</id>
    <title>Welcome to new undergraduates Lani, Noah,  Trevor, and Rohan</title>
    <updated>2024-01-23T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;div class="ablog-post-excerpt docutils container"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lani will be working on understanding how problem formulation is/not described in current
ML research.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trevor and Noah will be joining Brendan to work on internal tooling for the lab.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
    <link href="https://sarahmbrown.org/news/2024-01-23-ugsp24/"/>
    <summary>Lani will be working on understanding how problem formulation is/not described in current
ML research.Trevor and Noah will be joining Brendan to work on internal tooling for the lab.</summary>
    <published>2024-01-23T00:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://sarahmbrown.org/news/2024-03-04-mc-wids/</id>
    <title>I gave a keynote at Middlebury College Women in Data Science conference</title>
    <updated>2024-03-04T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;div class="ablog-post-excerpt docutils container"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;title&lt;/strong&gt;  Data Science Skills in Unexpected Places&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;abstract&lt;/strong&gt; Data science is a highly interdisciplinary pursuit, combining computer science and statistics with domain expertise to make sense of data. This means as data scientists we must work closely with domain experts or develop enough domain expertise of our own for each project.  In this talk, I will share the story behind a few data science projects I have done: how high school social studies helped me develop a learning PTSD diagnosis, undergraduate advanced writing helps me measure understanding of fairness in AI, and how student leadership experiences help me design tools for data scientists to build better models.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
    <link href="https://sarahmbrown.org/news/2024-03-04-mc-wids/"/>
    <summary>title  Data Science Skills in Unexpected Placesabstract Data science is a highly interdisciplinary pursuit, combining computer science and statistics with domain expertise to make sense of data. This means as data scientists we must work closely with domain experts or develop enough domain expertise of our own for each project.  In this talk, I will share the story behind a few data science projects I have done: how high school social studies helped me develop a learning PTSD diagnosis, undergraduate advanced writing helps me measure understanding of fairness in AI, and how student leadership experiences help me design tools for data scientists to build better models.</summary>
    <published>2024-03-04T00:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
